

NICOLA GRECO

CONTACTS



+39 324 783 7371 niccogreek@gmail.com



github.com/Nicogreco2001

16/11/2001 - Rome, Italy

ABOUT ME

I'm a 22-year-old student with a keen interest in biology, including molecular-scale biology and evolutionary processes. I'm also delving into machine learning and deep learning for biological applications. I'Known for quick learning and responsibility. Check my GitHub for my Bachelor's thesis and projects.

SKILLS

- · Good Knowledge of R
- Knowledge of Python
- knowledge of PyMol
- Knowledge of R Markdown for presentations
- Knowledge of Cytoscape

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Winner of "Fee waiver for deserving students" at University of Rome "La Sapienza": Tax exemption for having graduated with 100/100 at high school and maintaining a GPA higher than 27

Courses and Certifications: C1 IELTS certificate - Wall Street English Rome (2023)

EDUCATION AND TRAINING:

09/2023 - CURRENT MSC BIOINFORMATICS AND BIOCOMPLEXITY - Utrecht University - Utrecht, Netherlands

09/2020 - 07/2023

BSC BIOINFORMATICS (110 cum laude/110) - University of Rome "La Sapienza" - Rome, Italy

- Main courses: Bioinformatics I-II, Complex Biomolecular Networks, Al and Machine Learning
- GPA: 29.5/30

09/2015 - 07/2020 HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA (100/100) - Liceo scientifico statale "G.B. Morgagni" - Rome, italy

· Scientific studies (Maths, Phisics, Biology)

WORK EXPERIENCES

02/2022 - 07/2023 **COURSE ORIENTATION FOR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENTS -**UNIVERSITY OF ROME "LA SAPIENZA" - ROME, ITALY

- Holding an online information desk to help students during application procedure to BSC Bioinformatics
- Participated to the Open Day to present my Bachelor's degree

04/2020 - 05/2020 **VOLUNTEER** - Caritas - Rome, Italy

Helping homeless people during Covid-19 lockdown